在最后一节
In this last
课程中，你将把 Claude 连接到 Figma MCP 服务器，
lesson, you'll connect Claude to the Figma MCP server
从而将设计原型图导入 Claude Code 并开发相应的应用程序。
to import a design mockup to Claude Code and develop the application.
让我们来点有趣的尝试。
Let's have some fun.
既然我们已经了解了如何使用 Claude Code 快速熟悉代码库、
Now that we've seen how to use Claude Code to get up to speed on code bases
创建应用程序以及在多种不同环境中工作，
to create applications and work across many different environments,
我想展示一下 Claude Code 与
I want to showcase a really powerful ability for Claude Code
MCP 服务器配合工作的强大能力——从 Figma 等工具中获取原型图，
to work alongside MCP servers, to take mockups from tools like Figma
并快速将它们转换为 Web 应用程序。
and turn them into web applications quickly.
为了实现这一点，
In order to do that.
我们将使用 Figma MCP 服务器。
We're going to be making use of the Figma MCP server.
为此，你需要一个 Figma 账号。
And in order to do that, you will need a Figma account.
如果你没有订阅 Figma 的开发模式（dev mode），
We'll also provide an alternative if you want to use that
我们也提供了一个备选方案。
without subscribing to Figma as dev mode.
我们还将使用 Playwright MCP 服务器，
We're also going to be using our Playwright MCP server,
以便分析 Figma 的原型图，生成必要的 HTML，
so that we can analyze a mock up from Figma, generate the necessary HTML
然后通过在浏览器中打开它来进行编程测试，
and then programmatically test that by opening it in the browser
并截取屏幕截图，以确定如何最好地与该应用程序进行交互。
and taking screenshots of how best to interact with this application.
由于我正在构建一个采用现代技术栈的
Since I'm building a front end application with a more modern technology
前端应用程序，我将使用 Next.js 来实现。
stack, I'm going to be using Next.js to do that.
我先在当前文件夹中创建一个
So I'm just going to start by creating a Next.js application
最新版本的 Next.js 应用程序。
with the latest version inside of the folder that I'm in.
我将遵循大部分默认设置，
I'll follow most of these same defaults, and I'll go ahead
并让它安装必要的依赖项。
and let it install the necessary dependencies.
如果你之前没用过 Next.js，那也没关系。
If you have not worked with Next.js before, that's more than fine.
只需要几条命令行指令，很快我们就能
It's a couple of command line commands and then will be in the browser
在浏览器中看到结果了。
before you know it.
在安装的过程中，让我们看看 Figma 里的原型图。
While this is installing, let's go take a look at the mockup that we have in Figma.
在 Figma 中，
In Figma,
我这里有一个仪表盘原型，我想利用
I have a mock right here for a dashboard that I'd like
美国联邦储备局的经济数据来构建它。
to build using Federal Reserve Economic data.
这个 Figma 原型在图层和
This mock right here in Figma is not the most detailed in terms
后台分析方面
of all the layers
并不是最详细的，但足以让我们开始。
and all the analytics behind, but this is enough to get me started.
在 Figma 中，首先要确保已进入
What I'm going to do in Figma is first, make sure that I have gone
“偏好设置”并选择了“启用开发模式 MCP 服务器”。
to preferences and selected enable dev mode MCP server.
选中后，我要复制这个特定的图层，
Once I have that selected, I'm going to take this particular layer
因为在指定如何使用 MCP 服务器时
that I have and copy it because I'm going to need
我会用到它。
that when I specify what to use with the MCP server.
成功创建 Next.js 应用程序后，我们需要向 Claude 添加
Now that I've successfully created this Next.js application, we need to add
用于 Figma 和 Playwright 的两个 MCP 服务器。
to Claude the two MCP servers that I want to use for Figma and for Playwright.
我将输入必要的命令
I'm going to go ahead and add the necessary
来引入 Figma 的 MCP 服务器。
command here to bring in the MCP server for Figma.
然后对 Playwright 执行同样的操作。
And then I'll do the same for Playwright.
我正在添加用于 Playwright 的 MCP 服务器，
So I'm going to add an MCP server for Playwright,
它使用特定的命令在本地启动。
and that is started locally using the following command.
尽管我们之前添加过它，但请记住
And even though we already added this, remember
我们现在处于一个独立的工程和环境中。
we're in a separate project and a separate environment.
它不会自动应用到我构建的每一个 Claude Code 应用程序中。
So this does not get applied to every single Claude Code application I built.
我们必须为每一个工程单独执行此操作。
We have to do this for each one to make sure I've done this correctly.
为了确保操作正确，我进入 Claude 并使用 /mcp 命令
I'm going to hop into Claude and I'm going to use the slash MCP command
进行检查。
to make sure this looks good.
可以看到这两个服务器都已连接。
If I take a look, I can see that both of these are connected.
查看开发模式 MCP 服务器，可以看到
And if I take a look at the dev mode MCP server, I can see
有五个可用工具：获取底层代码、获取图像、
there are five tools available to get underlying code, to get an image,
获取关于特定 Figma 原型的设计规则等。
to get design rules around a particular mock up that I have in Figma.
连接好 MCP 服务器后，
Now that we've connected to both of our MCP servers,
让我们要求 Claude 使用特定的 Figma 原型图
let's go and ask Claude to use the following Figma mockup
和 Figma MCP 服务器来分析并构建所需的底层代码。
and the Figma MCP server to analyze and build the underlying code necessary.
我们要它使用 recharts 库来创建图表，
We'll ask it to use the recharge library for creating charts,
然后使用 Playwright MCP 服务器检查应用程序的外观。
and then we'll check how this application looks using the Playwright MCP server.
但在操作之前，我想做一个快速改动。
But before I do this, I want to go ahead and make a quick change.
如果你能够进行此改动且
If you are able to make this change and you're
不在专业版计划中，你可以使用 Opus 作为不同的模型。
not on the pro plan, you can use Opus as a different model.
如果不行，Sonnet 也能胜任，但对于较复杂的任务，
If not, Sonnet will still do a fine job, but Opus will do
Opus 的表现会稍好一些。
slightly better for a little bit more of a complex task.
切换模型后，
Once I have switched to that model,
让我们运行提示词，看看效果如何。
let's go ahead and run our prompt and see how it does.
首先我们需要连接到 MCP 服务器。
Well, first need to connect to our MCP servers.
确保我们使用了正确的原型图以及读取
Make sure we use the correct mock up and the tools necessary
底层代码所需的工具。
to read the underlying code to power this mock.
这里可以看到正在使用 Figma 开发模式 MCP 服务器的 Get image 工具，
Here we can see we're using the Get image tool from the Figma dev MCP server,
随后使用 Get Code 工具获取原型背后的
followed by the Get Code tool to get the underlying code behind that
底层代码。然后我们将确保安装
mock. We'll then make sure we install
必要的依赖项。
the necessary dependencies using npm or the package manager.
我们可以看到这里还没安装，
And here we're going to see it's not installed.
所以 Claude Code 很可能会要求我们安装它。
So Claude Code is most likely going to ask us to install that.
我们确认安装并继续。
We'll do so and continue onwards.
由于我们在 Next.js 应用程序中，
Since we're inside of this Next.js application.
大部分工作将在 app 文件夹中完成。
We're going to be doing the majority of the work in the app folder.
我们将分析全局 CSS，并开始创建主仪表盘
We'll analyze any global CSS and here start creating the main dashboard
结构。在这里我们要添加一点元数据。
structure. Here we're going to add a little bit of metadata.
看起来不错。
And this looks good.
对于后续的编辑，我就让 Claude 直接运行。
So for future edits I'll just let Claude go ahead and run those.
我们现在要创建仪表盘布局，
We're now going to create the dashboard layout
并采用 React 中基于组件的架构来构建。
and build this with more of a component based architecture in react.
既然已经创建了底层结构，让我们确保一切
Now that we've created the underlying structure, let's start to make sure things
符合预期。
look as expected.
由于我已经在这里运行了服务器，我直接告诉 Claude：
And since I've already run the server here, I'm just going to say
“不要运行服务器，
don't run the server.
它已经在运行了，继续下一步。”
It's already running. Continue on.
现在我们要用 Playwright 进行测试。
We're now going to test with Playwright and take a look at how things are.
我们将导航到 localhost:3000。
We'll go ahead and navigate to localhost 3000.
并截图。
Take a picture of that as well.
让我们截图。
And let's go ahead and let it take a screenshot.
我们可以看到在 Playwright 中，
We can see here in Playwright.
到目前为止，与原型图相比效果还不错。
So far it's looking pretty good compared to the mock.
虽然在某些柱状图上有一些额外的样式，
We've got a little extra styling on some of these bars,
但相对于我们的原型图起点来说，这是一个非常好的开始。
but this is a pretty good start from where we began with the mock right over here.
事实上，我甚至认为这看起来更漂亮一些。
In fact, I'd actually argue this looks a little bit nicer.
我们仍会看到一些正在进行的更改。
We're still going to see some changes that are being made.
侧边栏的布局
There's a layout in the sidebar
需要修改，我们可以让 Claude
that needs to be modified, and we can always have Claude
反复迭代这个特定的原型。
go back and forth and iterate across this particular mock.
有一点很重要：这个 Figma 原型并没有
One important thing to mention is that this mock in Figma does
大量的图层和底层组件。
not have a tremendous amount of layers and underlying components.
所以，很大程度上取决于你所拥有的原型图质量。
So a lot of this is going to depend on the quality of the underlying mock
that you have.
但在极短的时间内，这是一个非常好的开始。
But this is a really good start with very minimal amount of time.
我们可以看到哪些已经构建完成，哪些是紧密匹配的。
We can see here what's been built and what's closely matching.
现在让我们看看情况。
Now let's take a look at how things are.
通过模型的一点工作，并使用 MCP 服务器
We can see with a little bit of work from the model and using MCP servers
来验证可视化效果和构建原型，
to verify visualizations and build off our mocks.
原本可能需要几天时间从头开始构建的工作，
Things that might have taken days to do and build from scratch
在几分钟内就能完成。
can be done over the course of minutes.
你可能会好奇接下来的步骤。
So you might be wondering what comes next here.
我们拥有的这个原型只是一个开始。
This mock that we have is just the start of what you might imagine building.
这些数据实际上可以通过 API 获取。
And this data is actually available through an API.
所以我可以要求 Claude Code：“使用
So I could ask Claude Code, populate these charts
来自美国联邦储备局经济数据的真实数据填充这些图表。”
with real world data from the Federal Reserve Economic data.
我们要让 Claude Code 使用它的 Web 搜索
We'll go ahead and ask Claude Code to use one of its web search
工具来寻找信息，以便用真实数据进行更新。
tools to go ahead and find information to update with actual data.
在这里我们将查看 CPI、失业率、收益率等。
Here we'll look at CPI, unemployment yields and so on.
你可以想象这些数据是你从后端获取的。
But you can imagine this might be data that you're fetching from a back end.
但在这里我们将展示 Claude 的研究能力：
But here we're going to showcase Claude's ability to research
研究如何使用 API 文档，如何获取数据。
how to work with the API documentation how to fetch data.
我们可能需要一个 API 密钥。
And it might be possible that we need an API key to do so.
在进行研究时，Claude 会让我们知道
So as we start doing some of this research, Claude is going to let us know
需要什么来确保一切按预期运行。在那个原型中，
what we need to make sure things are working as expected. In that mock,
导航栏里有几个部分
there were a couple other
只是为了视觉展示，
pieces in the nav bar that were just meant for visualizations,
但接下来我们可以添加任何我们想要的底层功能。
but we can add whatever underlying functionality we want next.
经过一番研究，它意识到为了
So after it's done some research, it realizes that in order for me
从联邦储备局获取真实数据，
to fetch actual data from the Federal Reserve,
我需要输入一个 API 密钥。
I'm going to need to put in an API key.
我可以去我的账户获取 API 密钥。
I can go ahead to my account, get an API key.
这是一个相对简单的过程。
This is a relatively simple process that you can see here.
有了 API 密钥后，它将开始
Once I have my API key, it's going to start writing
为我编写额外的代码来获取并视觉化展示数据。
additional code for me to fetch data and display data visually.
我要在这里更新我的 API 密钥。
So I'm going to go ahead and update my API key inside of here.
更新后，让我们看看 Claude 在
Now that I've updated the API key, let's see where cloud is at
构建额外数据方面进展如何。
with building additional data.
它现在编写了一个获取经济数据的服务。
It's now written a service to fetch economic data.
我们现在要更新仪表盘，并使用 API 获取真实数据。
We're now going to update the dashboard and fetch real data using our API.
我们将用 Playwright 对此进行测试。
We're going to test this in Playwright.
然后在浏览器中查看。
And we're going to go ahead and then take a look at what we have in the browser.
我们将从视觉上查看它的效果，
We'll go see how this looks visually.
以及是否需要修改任何底层代码使其
And if there's any underlying code that needs to be modified to make
更具吸引力。
this more visually appealing,
只需一点提示词引导，
with just a little bit of prompting,
我们就能从一个带有虚构数据的原型，
we can go from a mock with some fake data
演变为真正使用真实数据源的实时信息。
to actually using real world information across a true data source for this data.
完成后，我们回到 localhost:3000 看看。
When we're done, we'll head back to localhost 3000.
我们可以看到我们获取的数据
Take a look at what we have and see that the data
不再是虚构的，
that we'll be fetching is not something that's actually fictitious,
而是真实的失业率、十年期国债收益率等。
but real unemployment, ten year treasuries and so on.
我们在这里设置了很多内容
We set up quite a bit here
来代理我们的请求，以及更多的交互功能。
to proxy our requests and quite a few more interactive features.
让我们看看效果。
So let's go see what that looks like.
我们从一个只有虚构数据
We've gone from our mock here with some fake data
且功能不多的原型，在短时间内变成了如此强大的工具。
and not a lot of functionality to something quite powerful.
In just a short period of time.
我们加载的数据真实反映了
The data we're loading here has data that is actually reflective
现实世界的信息。
of real world information.
随着我们添加更多功能，
And as we imagine adding more functionality,
我们可以切换查看不同状态。
we can tab through for what this will look like.
通过 MCP 服务器从现实环境中提取数据
But with just a small amount of work with an MCP server pulling data
并基于 Figma 原型构建 UI，
from real world environments and building UI from Figma mocks,
你可以想象前端开发的效率能有多高，
you can start to imagine how quickly front end development can go,
特别是构建强大的真实世界界面。
especially for building powerful real world interfaces.
你可能想验证这些数据是否真的来自源头，
You might want to verify that this data is actually coming from the source,
我们通过这个详细功能实现了这一点。
and we built that here with this detailed functionality.
我们可以轻松查看数据的来源、外观，
So we can easily see where this data is coming from, what things look like,
并将其追溯回我们正在构建的仪表盘。
and track that back to the dashboards that we're building as well.
这里我们只展示了一些关键指标。
So right here we're just showing some key indicators.
但接下来的工作可能是开始构建我自己的界面，或使用
But maybe the next thing I want to do is start building my own interface or use
另一个关于通货膨胀、就业等主题的 Figma 原型。
another Figma mark for things like inflation, employment and so on.
我们将从这段数据开始，但我很想看看
So we'll start with this piece of data, but I'd love to see what else
你利用这个界面和触手可及的数据还能构建出什么。
you can build using this interface and all the data at your fingertips.